<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>trademarkhell.net</title>
	<subtitle>ramblings from the 21st century</subtitle>
	<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/"/>
	<updated>2024-09-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://trademarkhell.net/</id>
	<author>
		<name>trademark</name>
		<email>trademark@cock.li</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Pointless Blogs</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/pointlessblogs/"/>
		<updated>2024-09-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/pointlessblogs/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The internet is filled with blogs, if you somehow haven&#39;t noticed. Curiously, though, the majority of these blogs have absolutely nothing of substance, they&#39;re just pointless ramblings from some guy (sound familiar?). Someone has to be reading them, though, otherwise, why would they exist? Despite the fact that there is very obviously a target demographic for this medium, I simply can&#39;t imagine who that demographic is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No offense to the pour soul(s, even) reading this, but there&#39;s no way in hell I&#39;d read this. This site, along with a lot of blogs, is the digital version of a insane man&#39;s diary. Contrary to popular schizophrenic belief, I don&#39;t think many people go out and read diaries in their free time, so that doesn&#39;t fully answer my question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you look at it from a different perspective, I suppose you could consider online blogs to be the idiot equivalent of opinion columns, but there&#39;s a distinct difference between the two. Opinion columns are published because they&#39;re from people with educated, interesting opinions, blogs are published because the webmaster has too much free time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think that could be exactly why there&#39;s a demographic for blogs, though, they provide the opinions of people who have no real credentials to be sharing them, and in a way, I suppose that&#39;s entertaining, even if unintentionally. I mean, there&#39;s even a few blogs I keep up with, but I sure know it&#39;s not because I view them as experts in their fields, I just do so because they&#39;re entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blogs are more or less a somewhat more complex version of those comments you see on forums of idiot&#39;s claiming they know everything. If you combine enough of them, you almost get information out of them, and in the process, you get a lot of entertainment. I still do take pity on you if you willingly go to this blog, but I appreciate it nonetheless. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Quality vs Quantity (for websites)</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/qualityvsquantity/"/>
		<updated>2024-09-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/qualityvsquantity/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Do you ever see a  site and think a bit later &#39;Man that site was cool I want to see it again,&#39; that&#39;s probably just me, but it seems that half the time I go back to sites like that, they a completely different layout a week later. That&#39;s not to say I have anything against redesigning sites, I mean, most people have personal sites because they like making them. It&#39;s just that, when you&#39;re changing your site multiple times in just a few weeks, your site begins to lose it&#39;s identity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s almost impossible to establish a, for lack of a better word, site identity, when your site is always changing. Especially when the changes often result in mismatched page styling, and for some sites, just flat out dead links. Most people won&#39;t look at your site for more than 30 seconds, that&#39;s just how it is, the aesthetics of it are pretty much what define how your site is viewed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my, completely subjective and unstudied opinion, you should only really update your site layout when you have a solid plan in mind, and have actually learned things that make it fundamentally better than the previous layout. It&#39;s kinda pointless to keep pushing out new re-designs, over, and over, when they add nothing markedly better than the previous version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you somehow are a black magic practing wizard who learns a bunch of new things every week, then my bad, keep updating your layout weekly, I guess. I just think for the majority of people, it&#39;s best to sit on your current site design for a few weeks/months so that you can really think about what you like/dislike about it, and how to improve it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hell, I even have a new layout on the draftboard for this site, but I don&#39;t intend to publish it until I can really think of &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; it&#39;d be better. If it&#39;s just the same quality as before, but different looking, why bother? This is all just my 2 cents, and quite frankly, I don&#39;t know nearly enough about webdevelopment to actually be qualified to talk about any of this. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Site Templates Aren&#39;t a Bad Thing</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/Templates/"/>
		<updated>2024-09-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/Templates/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you use Neocities or Nekoweb at all, and spend any amount of time of time in the Recently Updated sections, odds are you&#39;ll notice a lot of the sites look the same. You either have dementia, or the sites are using templates. Template based sites have sorta gotten a bad reputation, and that&#39;s fair, they&#39;re usually pretty boring, but they serve an important role in the &#39;Indie Web Ecosystem&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, some people aren&#39;t born as perfect as me, lacking the W3Schools implant I got in a secret government facility. This means that they need to actually start somewhere, and usually, somewhere doesn&#39;t involve making a full website from scratch despite having no experience. Templates, especially simple ones like the sadgrl template, allow for people to get one foot in the door for webdesign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Odds are, if you have a personal site, at one point, you used a template for it. Hell, even this site was based on a template for 35 minutes, before I took it down because I thought it was boring. Templates basically exist to get more people into HTML/CSS in a less daunting way, because unless you&#39;re an idiot like I was, you won&#39;t try to make a whole site after an hour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;d also argue that templates save us from a lot of sites that&#39;d be even worse without a template, my first site is a testament to this. Templates pretty much teach you the fundamentals of golden ratio web-design, so you don&#39;t end up expanding your site horizontally for some reason. (like i did...) Templates are more or less the only thing saving us from even more white background sites with a single line of text saying &amp;quot;welcome to my site, i made this to escape social media, i&#39;ll add more soon&amp;quot; for 8 months straight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically, despite semi-popular belief, templates aren&#39;t going to destroy the indie web as you know it, just let people use them, maybe they&#39;ll make a custom layout eventually. If they don&#39;t, yeah, my bad, you can still boil them. Besides, the whole idea behind the indie web is that you control your site, why care about what other people do? TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The Decline of Computer Literacy</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/computerliteracy/"/>
		<updated>2024-09-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/computerliteracy/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I was recently talking with my brother, who has the misfortune of teaching CAD to secondary school students, and something I found interesting was that he had to teach the students how to use Windows for the first week of the class. Admittedly, I found it semi-absurd that students technologically-interested enough to take a CAD elective had to be taught how to use file explorer, but the more I thought about it, the more it made sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Students today are, for all intents and purposes, the first generation to have had access to touch-screen based devices for their whole lives. Kids aren&#39;t sitting down in front of the &#39;family computer&#39; anymore, they&#39;re using tablets and phones. These devices, whilst extremely powerful for what they are, utilize a fundamentally different method of interaction than a computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think that&#39;s a big reason why we&#39;re seeing non, with a lack of a better word, nerdy, teenagers staring at the keyboard as they type and asking questions about basic computer usage. For those not into computing as a hobby, or not yet in the workforce, computers seem to have become largely obsolete.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even in the schools where computers are used on a regular basis, Chromebooks are often used, so students, whilst great at typing, lack knowledge of the Mac/Windows operating systems that they&#39;ll likely use for work. I also just hate Chromebooks as a whole, but I don&#39;t get paid enough to write more about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t a bad thing per se, I mean, it&#39;s inevitable that technology changeas over time, but I do think it&#39;s important for people to at least have a fundamental understanding of computer usage prior to entering the workforce.  I suppose with all the notes you take in university, that&#39;ll be taken care of. Schools could re-implement computer classes, but I doubt that many schools are too eager to re-open their computer labs after all these years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t to say that kids are just flat out not learning computing, either, There&#39;s plenty of teenagers on Nekoweb/Neocities with sites, it just seems as though, in general, less do. It&#39;s more of a hobby now, as opposed to a mandate like it once was. From an irrational standpoint it kinda annoys me that less people use computers, but it only makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tl;dr: i&#39;m mad about technology changing. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>CRTs Are Still Better Than LCDs</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ihatelcds/"/>
		<updated>2024-09-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ihatelcds/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;For years I was one of those pretentious people who resisted the switch from CRT to LCD monitors, but then we all kinda forgot about being pretentious and went to LCD anyways. I still do stand by this point though, as my unfortunate hobby choice of collecting old computers means I have quite a few CRT monitors. Even today, I feel as though the motion clarity and color on CRTs is far better than what we get on LCDs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the 2000s there was a major debate over LCD vs CRT monitors, mostly due to input lag. This debate largely became obsolete when CRT monitors stopped being produced, as the decision was effectively made for us, but the issue has yet to go away. Modern &amp;quot;gaming&amp;quot; monitors, even with their 165hz refresh rates, still have a 4-6ms input lag. Using milliseconds as a unit of measurement probably sounds absurd to any normal person, but for those playing competitive games and beat &#39;em up games, this can actually make a difference. You&#39;re effectively having a few frames between you hitting W on your keyboard and you actually moving, which can make all the difference. CRTs have zero input lag, as there&#39;s nothing digital going on, it&#39;s just an analogue signal being beamed up as soon as it get&#39;s received.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, the previous example only really applies to the most mentally compromised of computer users, such as myself, but I suspect this one will resonate with more people. If you&#39;ve done just about anything on an LCD display, odds are you&#39;ve noticed that the color black tends to appear as more of a grey. This is due to the fact that LCD monitors need to have a backlight on constantly, and as such, a &#39;true&#39; black can&#39;t really be made. CRT monitors never had this issue, as every individual piece of the screen was drawn independently from one another, so black areas simply had nothing at all. This color clarity probably doesn&#39;t matter as much to those who just play games or answer emails, but as someone who frequently consumes media on my LCD display, it irrationally annoys me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically, if you care at all about motion clarity or color clarity, a CRT is &lt;em&gt;technically&lt;/em&gt; better. LCDs are a lot easier to come by nowadays, though, and come in a much wider range of sizes. Besides, do you really want to deal with a CRT nowadays? Probably not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&#39;s one specific display technology I haven&#39;t mentioned, however, OLED. OLED is effectively the modern manifestation of the CRT, as they both use extremely similar methods for display. OLED has near zero input lag, and perfect blacks, but it does suffer from one thing. It&#39;s expensive as hell. In 5 years I do believe OLED will be the best display method, but up until then, I&#39;m gonna have to pass on a $1000 monitor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article strategically ignored the fact that CRT monitors are absolute behemoths and super finicky at times, but I did want to shill my favorite display technology. Which is really better? I don&#39;t really know, but I don&#39;t care either, I use both. Use CRTs if you like radiation, I guess. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>trademarkhell.net Month in Review</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/August24/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/August24/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So, it&#39;s the end of August now, and that means the current iteration of trademarkhell.net is about a month old. It&#39;s not perfect, and I&#39;m still not really sure why I have this site, but none the less, here we are. The first article I published to this site had a whole paragraph about why I disliked the way the site looked, and quite frankly, that sentiment remains, but I do at least have plans for the next minor revision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t have any intentions to fundamentally change this website operates, and, against my own better judgement, I&#39;ll stay true to my promise of daily articles for at least another month. There&#39;ll be some minor layout changes in the coming days, as I&#39;ve been meaning to move the navbar to the right, and make articles only 700px wide. In general, though, it&#39;ll be the same site, as I don&#39;t have any better ideas just yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website has garnered a lot more attention than I ever expected it to, and I&#39;m extremely grateful to those who have interacted with this site in one way or another. Admittedly, though, I don&#39;t think the attention this site has received is proportional to the minimal effort I put into it whatsoever. Please do consider going past the first page of Nekoweb, there&#39;s a lot of interesting sites to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do feel as though I should at least briefly touch on the statistics of the site, mostly for my own sake. The site currently has 11815 visits, and 59 Nekoweb followers. I touched further on the rate of growth a few days ago, so I won&#39;t dive into that here. I don&#39;t really know how I ended up here, but once again, thanks everyone, watching the funny numbers going up is very satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t really have all that much more to say, to be honest. Nothing will really change, which also means that I&#39;ve probably broken the indie web curse of dropping your site after 3 days, no promises, though. See you at the next article, I suppose. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/killmenow.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot; An image from the manga &#39;Watamote&#39; in which the main character says &#39; Just kill me now&#39; &quot; height=&quot;270px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt; 
pic unrelated i just needed an excuse to use it</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Discord and the Death of Forums</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/discord/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/discord/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you partake in any semi-niche interest, odds are you joined a Discord server to get information on it. It wasn&#39;t always this cumbersome, though, you used to be able to look just about anything up, and a result from the subject&#39;s forum would show up. Forums were thse bastions of knowledge (and misinformation) that largely disappeared both from search results, and from the internet itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t really a surprising development, I mean, Discord is free, and it costs money to host a forum, but it&#39;s very evident Discord wasn&#39;t intended for this. Discord server messages don&#39;t show up on search engines, and Discord&#39;s message look-up function is primitive at best. This leads to questions being asked, or forgotten about, over and over, and the responses, if even sent, being basic at best.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not to mention the fact that Discord lacks any (properly implemented) threads function, meaning that the questions that do get answered well inevitably get buried with a 500 message shitposting exchange that&#39;s happening at the same time. Discord is not a bad platform, but it&#39;s an awful place to share information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s not as though Discord is the only free platform available, either, even Reddit, despite suffering from being Reddit, at least shows up on search results and has a proper post look-up function. Literally everything is better than Discord, and there&#39;s almost always some community members willing to shill out the money to keep a forum going. That&#39;s how audiphile and car forums have survived for so long. I use my Tapeheads account daily, and I don&#39;t see that forum going anywhere, despite it&#39;s age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more communities that switch to Discord, the more information is made private, it&#39;s that simple. I&#39;m not going to try and pretend that Discord is awful, or that forums are the greatest online innovation ever, I&#39;m just trying to put it as it is. I&#39;ll always believe that the web should have easily accessible information on any subject, no matter how niche and community oriented it may be, and forums are the easiest medium for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you for some reason hold a prominent position in the online community of something, please, please, get people together for a forum. Forums are by far the best way to spread knowledge on poorly documented topics, and basically everything I&#39;ve ever done to my stereo equipment or cars has come from a forum thread. The internet is a place for sharing info, make the info easily accessible. I didn&#39;t make this article super long because it&#39;d be pointless, but do keep it in mind. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>English Is Actually Pretty Interesting</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/english/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/english/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re here, you probably understand English, if not, I don&#39;t really know how you read this. English, since the Treaty of Versailles in 1919, has effectively become the generic lingua franca that you either know or want to know. This has placed English in a very different position from other commonly studied languages. Those who study French or Latin often do so recreationally, and, as such, will study the history and complexities of the languages. Many who study English, however, seem to predominantly focus on the fundamentals of the language itself, disregarding it&#39;s history and often redunant minor grammatical quirks.  I think that the position English holds in this aspect is quite unfortunate, and, because of this, I&#39;m here to educate you all about &amp;quot;random shit i think is kinda cool about english&amp;quot; (patent pending).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;English, tragically, originated in England, and as such, met the requirement of being kinda bad for mawhile, being far less eloquent than many other languages for the bulk of it&#39;s existence.  This was in large part because English was a peasant&#39;s language, originating from various West Germanic dialects, with little external influence from the traditional Romance languages. This meant that English, whilst extremely common, lacked the vocabulary many other languages had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;English&#39;s reputation of being a peasant&#39;s language that scholars would avoid with a 50 foot poll began to change around the 14th-16th century, however. People came to the shocking conclusion &amp;quot;wait why dont we just add more words,&amp;quot; and bam, now English is 28% Latin, and 28% French, problem solved. Around this time is when English began to gain a reputation globally, and literary works began to get translated into English, most notably including religious texts. For the first time, too, English author&#39;s began to gain global popularity, since they were able to actually make compelling written works for the first time, such as Shakespeare and Milton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The language didn&#39;t really gain significant global recognition until the rise of the British Empire and the United States, though, and even with the rise of these two powers, French was still the language of diplomacy and research. English didn&#39;t truly become the lingua franca of the world until the aforementioned Treaty of Versailles in 1919, which was led by the United States. The United States, despite being in France, hosted the meeting in English. In my eyes, this represented the pivotal point where English gained true global significance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This peculiar history is exactly why English is so strange now, even if it may not seem so to native speakers. You&#39;re effectively speaking a language with German grammar and German base words, but with a little French and Latin vocabulary thrown in. This is exactly why English is so commonly regarded as a hard language to learn, it wasn&#39;t a language built by scholars, it was a product of the common man throwing components into a language over centuries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Almost every other language was made with every single concept having a purpose, designed only to be written by the highest classes of society, but not English, and that&#39;s why I find English so interesting. English, against all odds, has become the dominant language for literary works, research, and politics, despite being so distanced from such concepts at it&#39;s creation. I&#39;ve studied numerous languages, both willingly, and out of necesity due to moving,  I haven&#39;t even lived in an English speaking country for years, but man, it&#39;ll always be my favorite language. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Planned Obsolescence in Technology</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/plannedobsolescence/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/plannedobsolescence/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My phone is currently getting the battery replaced, and that got me curious about how I even ended up in the position. Even just 15 years ago, nearly every device had a single panel to pop off if you wanted to replace the battery, and every other component could be replaced with a rudimentary tool set. Nowadays, however, it seems as though just about every device, regardless of size, feels the need to make it as hard as humanly possible to replace any components. I believe that this is a result of planned obsolescence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Planned obsolescence, in laymans terms, is the concept of a product intentionally being designed to last a specific period of time. In modern technology, this seems to be present in numerous areas, far more than there once was in technology. I&#39;m not an engineer, but I am certified terminally online, so I&#39;ll try to explain how this is happening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As aforementioned, electronics are now harder to open than ever before, many phones require specific tools to open them, and even past that point, use proprietary screwheads. This allows for the distributors of the devices, and a select group of repair stores willing to shill out the money for the required equipment, to have the ability to charge astronomical prices for repairs. I mean, why repair your phone if you can get a new one for almost the same amount? That&#39;s what makes it planned obsolescence, your phone, tablet, or really any portable device&#39;s shelf-life is effectively determined by the life of components that would previously be replaced, such as capacitors or batteries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t solely a hardware issue, either, odds are if you use Windows you&#39;re being pushed heavily to &amp;quot;upgrade&amp;quot; to Windows 11, regardless of your current hardware, despite it&#39;s significantly higher operating requirements. This will ultimately result in your computer running slower, and in the process, lead to a large portion of individuals just going out and buying a new one, for your computer was magically made obsolete through an update. The same applies to a lot of modern phones, I mean, just look at how slow a phone runs after 5 years of updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything I&#39;m writing is rather pointless if I don&#39;t give a basis for comparison, though, so let me take a device from a company that&#39;s gained a reputation for being anti-consumer as of late. The iPod Video 5th generation, a device which released in 2005, and was nearly as popular as the iPhone is now. This isn&#39;t some niche tech-nerd marketed product, yet with a pry tool and a #1 phillips-head screwdriver, every single component in it can be replaced. Switching out the battery is as simple as prying it open, disconnecting the old one, connecting the new one, and pushing it back together. It was that easy on an &lt;em&gt;Apple&lt;/em&gt; product.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, what changed, exactly? Consumer culture did, I suppose, for years technology was just a tool, rather than a status symbol, so companies had to make good, long lasting, tools. As of late, however, especially with the later iPods, and modern smartphones, having a new device has become something desirable. Companies are able to get away with making devices that go bad because they&#39;re targeting an audience who&#39;ll go and buy a new one a year later anyways. This&#39;ll leave those who don&#39;t want to in a rather poor position, but in a few years when your phone only last 2 hours on a charge, what choice do you have?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is all just a really long way to say that companies realized we&#39;re suckers, and now we get to deal with shitty technology that&#39;s designed to be awful to use after a few years. Kinda unfortunate, but nothing we can really do about it, go move to a country with 2G and use a Nokia, I guess. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Does Content Influence Site Growth?</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/sitecontent/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/sitecontent/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This site, trademarkhell.net, suffered from being rather purposeless in July of 2024, it&#39;s first month of existence, and as such, I arbitrarily decided to make it a blog site. Admittedly, I mostly did this because I wasn&#39;t any good at making web-design resources, or sites, for that matter. Solely making a blog, however, seemed boring, so I wanted to also test how activity would influence the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to my site&#39;s revision being pushed, on the 8th of August, the site had 27 followers, and 3782 views. The site was originally published on the 1st of July, so this rougly equates to 0.69 followers per day up, and 97 views a day. This previous version was very much the stereotypical indie web site, it had bright colors, anime girls, was rarely updated, and had virtually 0 content, but to some demographics, it may have been considered visually appealing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current site you&#39;re on, is the culmination of me attempting the opposite, a site that&#39;s styled in an extremely boring manner, but is filled with content, in the form of daily articles. This site version has been up since the 8th of August, and at the time of writing, has 54 followers and 9996 visits after 19 days up. This means that the site has doubled it&#39;s followers, and gained 6,214 more views, equating to 1.4 followers per day and 327 views per day. Furthermore, not including this article, the site has 23 articles currently up, equating to 1.17 followers per article posted, and 230 views per article posted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is solely ancedotal, but at least for my case, I do believe it shows that freqeuntly updating your site with content does have genuine benefits to gaining popularity. I don&#39;t have any evidence to back this up, but I imagine this is likely due to the fact that repeat viewers make up much of the views for content-based sites. Which makes sense, given there&#39;s actual reason to return to the sites, as opposed to a cool looking site that was updated 8 months ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I can&#39;t say these results will really change the way I run this site, if I was smart I&#39;d just drop this site completely now that my pseudo-experiment is done, but I can&#39;t bring myself to. I suspect that I&#39;ll keep publishing articles daily until I run out of things to say, which will likely be never, as I love talking. Moral of the story, update your site. TM out. My conquest for internet numbers will continue.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A Brief Overview of the PC-9821 Cs2</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/pc98/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/pc98/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I pride myself in my ability to publish articles of absolutely no substance, but from time to time, it is my duty to publish actual content to this site. I&#39;m fulfilling this contractual obligation by writing an article on one of my favorite computers of all time, and probably the one I mess around with the most, the PC-9821 Cs2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m currently in the middle of recapping the monitor that usually accompanies it, but here&#39;s a photo of the device itself:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/pc98.jpg&quot; alt=&quot; A photo of the aforementioned PC-98&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;If you think this looks like a generic computer from the mid 90s, you&#39;re correct. The PC-98 was NEC&#39;s answer to the increasingly popular IBM PC standard in the west, which I also wrote an article on. The IBM PC lacked the ability to display Japanese characters, and as such, a Japanese variant came in the form of the PC-88, originally, and later the PC-98 (divided into pc-9801 and pc-9821). Fundamentally, this is a rather standard computer, but it has vastly superior graphics to the IBM PC compatible&#39;s of it&#39;s time, due to the fact that the Japanese characters required far greater resolution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In effect, by making a machine capable of displaying comprehensible text, they also made a pixel-art based visual novel/shmup machine, oh, and eroge, lots of that, for some reason. So whilst people everywhere else got to enjoy these stunning graphics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/doom1.png&quot; alt=&quot; A screenshot from Doom&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt; 
(Doom screenshot; from Wikipedia)
&lt;p&gt;Japan got this:
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/policenautsop.png&quot; alt=&quot; A screenshot from the Policenauts opening&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
(Screenshot from Policenauts; taken from Reddit. hideo kojima made this VN and it&#39;s one of my favorites of all time, read it.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;cool-but-what-actually-made-these-graphics&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Cool, but what actually made these graphics? &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/pc98/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PC-9821 CS2, what I have, and what I&#39;ll be covering, is, in most ways, very comprable to IBM PC compatibles of the same time. It features an Intel 486SX with a 33mhz clock speed, 4.6mb of ram, a 340mb HDD from the factory, dual 3.5&amp;quot; floppy drives, and a CD-Rom drive. What made the device stand out was what it output through analogue RGB, 640x480 with 256 colors. At the time, 1992 to be exact, The IBM ecosystem was using VGA, which output 640x480 with merely 16 colors, or 320x200 with 256 colors. In effect, you had to choose between color and resolution on the IBM PC, but not with the 98, which is why the screenshot from it looked so much better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is all just a really long way to say that the PC-98 just flat out had better graphics, in part because it was necesitated by the Japanese character set, which would&#39;ve been virtually illegible at 320x200. For all the linguistics people out there, make languages more complicated so that we get cooler graphics, please and thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-sound-is-pretty-cool-too&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;The sound is pretty cool too.. &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/pc98/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t intend for this article to just be me ragging on IBM for a page, but I do feel as though the YM3812 sound cards IBM PCs used were, whilst charming, rather ineffective. The YM3812 is the Yamaha produced chip that you&#39;ll find on Soundblaster cards and similar from the era, and is also what you&#39;ll hear playing the soundtrack to Doom, and in some cases, Half-life. It&#39;s not bad by any means, but was very limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PC-98 used the YM2203 chip, also from Yamaha, which utilized FM synthesis. I could probably try to explain what makes this better, but instead I&#39;ll just attach a piece of music from it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is Vanishing Dream ~ Lost Dream (Kana&#39;s theme) from Touhou 3&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;60&quot; src=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1yoQwZih2I0OzrxtPJebtDgP0K1VcuEuQ/preview?usp=drivesdk&quot;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t to discredit the musicians who composed the soundtracks of IBM PC games, either, but rather to show the fact that the PC-98 allowed for music to, y&#39;know, sound like music, as opposed to videogame music. I found that it really added a lot, especially when playing visual novels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-games&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;The Games &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/pc98/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m just going to be fully honest here, the games may&#39;ve looked better, but the IBM PC and it&#39;s compatibles had a significantly larger, and often better catalogue. The PC-98 only really had the IBM PC beat out in two areas, shmups, and visual novels. Most modern shmup franchises got their start on the PC-98, and to be honest, still hold up extremely well today. Visual novels from the 98 era have also fared much better graphically than their late 90s/early 2000s successors, when Japan switched to the IBM PC format, still looking quite stunning today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;d only really consider getting a 98 if you&#39;re a complete dweeb who likes visual novels (me) or if you&#39;re a complete dweeb who likes shmups (me). There&#39;s a decent bit of RPGs and other games, but in large part, go to consoles for those. The 98 was still a business machine at the end of the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-s-the-point&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;What&#39;s the point? &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/pc98/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&#39;s no point to this article, I just think the PC-98 series, and my PC-9821 Cs2 are cool as hell, and I wanted to share it with others. If you do want to pick one up, you can still get them for reasonably cheap, assuming you&#39;re willing to recap them, and are able to supply them with the appropriate voltage. As always, if you have any questions on the subject, I&#39;ll try to answer them, but no promises. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Wait, Anime Became Popular?</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/anime/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/anime/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Anime, for years, was a relatively niche interest that you&#39;d mostly only hear about from image boards, Reddit, and when it was being used as a joke punchline. However, in recent years, it seems to have, somehow, gone relatively mainstream. As a cardholding dweeb, I found this rather strange at first, until I realized that, in practice, it was pretty inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Up until the past ten or so years, the only ways to really watch anime outside of Japan were to get lucky and have the show get an official DVD release abroad, get sorta lucky and find the series uploaded in 240p on Youtube before it got taken down, or to be reasonably computer literate and use a torrent. There was no real mainstream way to watch most anime, you had to actively seek it out, and odds are, you&#39;d never even know to seek it out unless you were involved in certain internet circles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, that&#39;s not to say that anime was some completely non-existent outside of japan, only lurking in the shadows of the internet, certain shows were aired on live TV outside of Japan. Death Note and Pokemon fall into this category, among others, but this was far from the norm. Furthermore, these shows were dubbed over and usually works that were targeted towards the youth, so they occupied a position akin to that of cartoons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, in the past ten or so years, the ease of access for watching just about any piece of anime changed radically, with the advent of streaming sites. These sites, both legal, and piracy-based, made it far easier than ever before to access anime with subtitles or dub tracks, and made the previously standard elitist torrenting circles obsolete. It&#39;s common sense that if something is easier, more people will do it, and by extension, more people will talk about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t think that the popularity of anime in recent years can be solely attributed to ease of use, however, as there had to be some other external push to justify people wanting to consume the medium. This came in the form of the COVID-19 pandemic, which more or less gave the bulk of the world&#39;s population an excuse to sit around and do nothing, and in the process, necesitated that they had something to do. Anime consumption presented itself as a (usually) free time waster that was remarkebly easy, and bam, the loser population of planet Earth multiplied fivefold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s not as though these people just magically lost interest in their newfound hobby when the pandemic began to wind down, and as such, here we are, with anime being more popular globally than ever before. Is this a good thing? Probably not, but who cares. Have fun watching AOT with your mom, because I got to endure that experience. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;also, helsing ultimate is actually a masterpiece and i&#39;ll always stand by that&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The Demographics of the Indie Web</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/indiewebdemographics/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/indiewebdemographics/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you haven&#39;t noticed already, the indie web tends to attract various peculiar demographics, and if you think you aren&#39;t peculiar, yes you are, you run a personal site in 2024. These demographics all culminate to create the bullet hole ridden neighborhood that is the indie web community, yet, I don&#39;t think anyone&#39;s ever formaly declared these demographics. To be clear, I&#39;m not going to either, but I sure as hell will try.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel as though the majority of indie web sites can be viewed as fitting into one of the following three categories, sites built for style, sites built for content, and sites built for insanity. The latter of the three is a more fringe definition, but you&#39;ll certainly know when you see one. It&#39;s obvious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I consider to be &#39;sites built for style&#39; are, in effect, the sites you often see that look extremely well made, yet somehow have every link off of the homepage leading to a 404, despite being up for months. Typical standout features you&#39;ll see on sites falling into this category are heavily stylized divs (scanline filters, non-standard shapes, etc), custom made graphics, and for some reason, autoplay music. These sites are the fashion statements of the indie web, and despite having no real purpose, the indie web would be terribly boring without them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, &#39;sites built for content&#39; aren&#39;t inherently bad looking sites, but these are the types of sites that tend to be built for an explicit purpose. These are the types of sites that are being used as portfolios, blogs, and at times, even just as link hubs. These sites often are visually appealing, but, not at the cost of legibility and convenience as many falling in the &#39;sites built for style&#39; category do. I find these sites to be the most interesting to interact with, but probably the least interesting to look at.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last category, &#39;sites built for insanity&#39; is a rather nebulous one, but I&#39;ll do my best to explain them. These are the sites solely dedicated to single characters and topics, imagine a shrine, but 50fold. There&#39;s not a large amount of these sites due to the sheer amount of effort they take, but it&#39;s always very clear when you&#39;ve clicked on one. Despite the name I&#39;ve given this category, I do find these sites to be rather endearing, even if they may be the product of an insane man&#39;s work. They&#39;re the web equivalent of TempleOS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From my observations, I think it&#39;s hard to find a site that won&#39;t fit into one of these three categories, however, I could be wrong. If a new era of victims stumbles upon the indie web, and makes new sites, please do notify me, for I&#39;ll be certain to add them. I mostly just wrote this article for fun, as I&#39;m in the middle of working on my PC-98 article, don&#39;t take it to seriously, or do, I don&#39;t really mind. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>AI Does More Than Steal Jobs and Art</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ai/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ai/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you look around on Nekoweb, which is filled with artists, you&#39;ll inevitably see a lot of webmasters strongly opposed to AI in it&#39;s entirety. I feel as though this perspective is inherently flawed, however, for the AI you use to cheat on homework, make low quality anime girls, and roleplay with is very different from the AI that is allowing scientific and medical research to be done at a rate faster than ever before, thanks to machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I find it ignorant to consider the entirety of AI to be this terrible thing, when, in practice, it is one of man&#39;s greatest innovations of recent years. It&#39;s fundamentally changing the way research on cancer and other diseases is being approached (i am not citing stuff on &amp;quot;trademarkhell.net&amp;quot; but here&#39;s a link https://www.cancer.gov/research/infrastructure/artificial-intelligence). If the cost of better understanding a disease that&#39;s stumped researchers is some crappy AI generated art, then I think that&#39;s worth it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also see a lot of people which (justifiably) dislike AI due to the inherent belief that it will take human jobs. In my eyes, however, this is simply improbable for the majority of jobs, because governments will likely pass regulations forbidding it. Governments would end up being the people having to deal with the homeless cleanup, unemployment checks, and reduction in tax income, and believe it or not, they don&#39;t want to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AI in and of itself has already begun to become a buzzword similar to what happened with NFTs and a lot of cryptocurrencies. I think the most likely outcome will be that it simply becomes a tool for research (and larping...) like any other, albiet far more efficient. So, no, your thriving job as an artist in which you depict catgirls 7/11 parking lots will likely not be at risk, nobody really wants an AI version..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s just another product of a constantly changing era that we&#39;ll have to adapt to, nothing more, nothing less. It&#39;s foolish to feel as though this&#39;ll be the end of all jobs and art as a whole. Sure, some fields may change to a degree, but I doubt that it&#39;ll be the radical shift that some people suspect it to be. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/ruukoto.png&quot; alt=&quot; Ruukoto from the Touhou Franchise; a robot maid &quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;ruukoto from touhou is the future of ai....&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Why Neocities/Nekoweb?</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/whyneocitiesnekoweb/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/whyneocitiesnekoweb/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;When you click on a personal website, odds are you&#39;ll see &#39;neocities&#39;, or, in some cases, &#39;nekoweb&#39; in the link. However, there&#39;s nothing that clearly makes these two better than other free webhosts, at first glance. There&#39;s plenty of other webhosts with similar or higher bandwidth/storage, and at times, even free custom domain support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite this, I recently realized what it was that really differentiated Neocities and Nekoweb from other webhosts, they satiate the desire for approval that many of us have gotten from social media. Nekoweb and Neocities both have followers and accessible view counters, and Neocities features profiles and comment sections, not all that different to how social media pages function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People, at least in my opinion, default to these hosts because they seek the validation that social media gives them, without using social media itself. People clearly aren&#39;t just ignoring the statistics and comment sections on their sites. You&#39;ll see countless sites, including mine, which display their followers and views directly on the homepage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These hosts are effectively used for the easy dopamine they provide in the form of increasing numbers, the same reason people use social media. That&#39;s why they&#39;re so much more popular than other site hosts with no homepage and no followers. They serve as a medium for fulfilling the desire for approval that so many people have gained over the years, but hey, I guess it beats getting approval through social media.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s not to say that either host is bad, I mean, I pay for the premium tier of Nekoweb and pray to Dimden fourty-two times a day so that he won&#39;t delete my site. Popular webhosts have always at least had some aspect akin to that of social media. Geocities was originally  named as such because it featured individual cities for each type of website, and in these cities were HTML based chatrooms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Socialization, and the approval that stems from it seems to have always been a major influencing factor for the majority of personal site webmasters, and the decisions they make. It&#39;s simply grown more relevant as of late with the increasing popularity of social media. It&#39;s human nature to want people to appreciate your work, and I assume that the majority of people making websites aren&#39;t robots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could probably try to stretch this out further, but I made my point. Keep in mind that this is all based on my opinions, TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Personal Sites Are a Result of Egotism</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/personalsiteego/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/personalsiteego/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Let me preface everything I write here with one thing, you&#39;re currently on a personal site. The very act of creating a personal site is an act of egotism. Egotism is defined by Oxford Languages as &amp;quot;the practice of talking and thinking about oneself excessively because of an undue sense of self-importance.&amp;quot; Personal sites are solely dedicated to one&#39;s self and their interests, it&#39;s hard to argue that they are not the product of egotism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Egotism, itself, however, is only viewed negatively because of the preconceived notion we hold of it. I&#39;d argue that a large part of what makes personal sites so interesting is that they were crafted by people so engrossed in themselves, and by extension, their interests. People don&#39;t dedicate hours to making elaborate shrines on their sites as a service to others, they do it because they enjoy the subject it&#39;s dedicated to. Blogs don&#39;t exist because people feel as thought they&#39;re providing some service to the community by sharing their ramblings, they just want to write about themselves and what they think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There wouldn&#39;t be a single non commercial site on the internet not run by a major figure if people weren&#39;t at least a little egotistical. It&#39;s because of this, that I feel as thought the concept of egotism being bad, at least in this case, is rather antiquated. Some of the most interesting takes I&#39;ve read are the product of people so obsessed with their opinions that they felt the need to write full-length articles on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Egotism, in my eyes, is the foundation of the majority of creative works. It&#39;s not as though authors or artists magically start as important people, it&#39;s a necesity for them to have an unjust sense of self-importance to even present their works or contact a publisher. Personal sites are obviously a far more literal example of this, but I feel as though the point remains. A personal site not based on egotism would be the personal equivalent of Dictionary.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is not a criticism of personal sites, nor is it a criticism of egotism, rather, it&#39;s a criticism of the modern perspective of egotism. Egotism, despite the numerous poor traits it&#39;s associated with, can be the result of rather interesting things when used creatively. Personal sites could be considered an example of just that, and that&#39;s exactly why I enjoy looking through them so much, they serve as a window into how another person thinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal sites are effectively the most self-indulgent thing you can create on the internet. There isn&#39;t a single piece of logic behind making one that doesn&#39;t involve what the creator wants, or how they feel. It&#39;s all about an individual, and in some cases (i&#39;ll ignore the others), that leads to rather interesting sites. Those interesting sites made by interesting people are what justify the egotistical nature of the Indie Web, among any other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tl;dr: being an asshole is cool and awesome when it&#39;s under the pretense of web-development (gregory house photo related). TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/gregorhouse.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A photo of Gregory House from House MD&quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Advice for New Web Devs</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/newwebdevs/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/newwebdevs/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;There&#39;s not really a formal set of guidelines to web development, and I don&#39;t intend to make them, rather, my intention with this article is to make it so you don&#39;t have to completely remake your site after 3 weeks as I did. I&#39;ll mostly be covering things on the back-end that help with convenience, but I will touch briefly on accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The worst trend I&#39;ve been seeing as of late has to do with iframes. Iframes themselves aren&#39;t bad, and can be very useful, but improper usage of them is terrible to work with and terrible for the user. Iframes should not be used as a substitute for seperate pages, this makes your site a royal pain to work on, and effectively makes the site useless to screen reader users. If you need a way to keep a consistent layout on every page, either make a boiler plate layout you can copy paste, or put your site into an SSG with a templating engine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a similar templating note, make sure your site has a consistent navbar layout. It&#39;s fine to change the layout of the individual pages if you want to, but the navbar is effectively the core of how your site is operated. It&#39;s important for the layout of it to be consistent, as it allows the user to orient themselves, and if needed, return to a previous page. Don&#39;t be the type of person to have the navbar mysteriously disappear and just expect the user to go back manually, your site viewers are more lazy than you think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing I feel a lot of new web developers (myself included, my first site was a war crime) forget, is that people have different screen sizes than you. Just because your site works perfectly on your 4K monitor doesn&#39;t mean that the majority of users on a 1080p monitor won&#39;t end up with a horizontal scrollbar. Generally speaking, don&#39;t make your website any wider than 1024px, this means that basically anyone, regardless of monitor, will be able to use your site without scrolling horizontally. Build your site down, not to the sides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a similar note of screen variations, color temperature is another rather important one. About a month ago there was a rather interesting saga involving a user with a site that used grey text on a black background. This was perfectly legible for them, and anyone else using an OLED monitor, but for everyone else it was impossible to read. Stick to contrasting colors, there&#39;s a reason so many sites still go for grey and white and white and black.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/unlegible.png&quot; alt=&quot;black text on a grey background saying this isnt legible, sorry&quot; height=&quot;50px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is on a very different note, but don&#39;t feel the need to push your site out right away, I published my first site after a few hours of working on it, and it had aproximately nothing of substance. There&#39;s no need to rush your website out, take your time to get all the links filled out, nobody&#39;s going to mind waiting a few days to see your site. A more complete site is always better than a site with twenty links that all lead to nothing but a &amp;quot;sowwy coming soon&amp;quot; page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried to hit all the bases of things I&#39;ve noticed on others sites and from my old sites, but there&#39;s absolutely more things you&#39;ll end up learning through trial and error. If anyone else can think of some major things I missed, feel free to put them in the comments. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A Brief Overview of the IBM 5160</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ibm5160/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ibm5160/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The IBM 5160, or, the IBM PC XT, is the direct successor to the IBM 5160, the IBM PC. There&#39;s technically some motherboard differences between the two, but in practice, the only real difference is that the IBM 5160 came from the factory with a HDD, as opposed to the IBM PC, which came with dual 5.25&amp;quot; floppy drives. The IBM PC lineup has a very interesting history, but due to that deviating from the purpose of this article, all you really need to know is that the IBM PC was effectively the first readily available computer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;graphics&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Graphics &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ibm5160/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IBM PC XT was available with three different graphics cards, the Monochrome Display Adapter, the Color Graphics Adapter, and the Enhanced Graphics Adapter. The Monochrome Display Adapter, as the name suggests, gives you monochrome graphics, with 80 columns and 25 lines of text. It was intended to be paired with the IBM 5151, which was the stereotypical black and green terminal-esque monitor that we&#39;ve grown used to seeing in games such as Fallout. The Color Graphics Adapter, despite what the name may infer, barely gives you color, only giving you a limited palette of four colors at 320x200 . It was designed with the IBM 5153 in mind, and you can see a photo of mine running Microsoft Flight Simulator 3 (1988) below, in all of it&#39;s ugly glory. (Pardon the reflection)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/fs3closeup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A photo of my IBM 5160 running MFS3 &quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That brings us to the last, and least commonly used adapter, the Enhanced Graphics Adapter, it gave you proper 16 color graphics at 320x200, although came in at a lofty price, and was made obsolete by VGA shortly after it&#39;s release. It was intended to be paired with the IBM 5154.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In practice, all you really need to run the vast majority of IBM PC games is a CGA card, given it can display graphics, unlike the text-only MDA, however games will look much better with a EGA card, and if you&#39;re a heathen, a VGA card. What card you opt for really comes to budget and personal preference, I quite like the period-correct charm of the CGA card&#39;s graphics, but it&#39;s certainly an acquired taste.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;ram&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Ram &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ibm5160/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ram is probably the most important thing outside of your graphics card of choice that determines if you can run a game or not. The IBM 5160 was limited to 640kb of ram, but, in practice, the majority of computers you&#39;ll find will have a maximum of 256KB. This can be remedied by relatively inexpensive ram chips, and I highly advise doing so, as 400kb of RAM can be the difference between a slideshow and an actually enjoyable game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;storage&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Storage &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ibm5160/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IBM 5160 was equipped from the factory with one 5mb HDD, and one 5.25&amp;quot; floppy drive. 5MB likely sounds like very little storage, and in a world of 20MB flac files and 200GB games, it is, but at the time this was a rather impressive development. The earlier 5150 had no HDD, and exepcted the user to solely rely on a constant rotation of floppy disks, so this 5MB HDD effectively changed the way computers were operated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Odds are, however, this HDD will have lost it&#39;s magnetization many years ago by now, and will need to be replaced. This is where the wonders of modern technology make operating the computer much easier. Rather than hunting down an original HDD, you can install a XT-IDE card (or a offbrand, like i use), which allow you to use a compact flash card as your HDD. This means transferring files onto your IBM PC is as simple as dragging the files onto the compact flash card from your modern computer, and plugging it into the IBM PC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-there-any-realistic-use-case-for-this&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Is There Any Realistic Use Case For This? &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ibm5160/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IBM 5160 is a 41 year old piece of technology, and for the majority of tasks, completely useless. Despite this, I find a certain joy in playing through the vast catalogue of 80s DOS games on it, and at times, programming in C or BASIC You can do literally everything an IBM PC can on a new PC with DOSBox, but something just hits different about doing it on original hardware. It&#39;s just cool, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-personal-setup&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;My Personal Setup &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ibm5160/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally run a fully recapped IBM 5160, with a CGA graphics card, a few other connectivity cards, a 3-COM Etherlink, which allows me to connect to BBS Boards through ethernet, an IBM Model M keyboard, 640KB of ram, a 500MB compact flash card, and a IBM 5153 monitor. For My personal needs, this is the ultimate setup, I find that it combines modern convenience with with reasonably believable period-correct hardware. There&#39;s nothing I can think of that I&#39;d change with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/5160setup82024.png&quot; alt=&quot;My 5160 setup&quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Conclusion &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ibm5160/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a lot different than my previous articles, and I hope to publish more semi-constructive works about things I find interesting. If you have questions about the IBM PC lineup for some reason, feel free to ask me, I like to think of myself as semi-knowledgeable about them. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Why Use About Me Sections?</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/aboutmesections/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/aboutmesections/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you look at a personal website, odds are you&#39;ll see a link on the navbar that goes to something roughly equating to an about me section. At first glance, this does make sense, I mean it&#39;s a personal site, you&#39;d want to put details about the person who runs the site on it. However, it&#39;s exactly because personal sites are meant to be personal that I oppose about me sections. In everyday conversations you don&#39;t get handed a list of bullet points about the person you&#39;re talking to, you deduce who they are based on how they act and what they say. I think that personal sites should operate in a similar manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally feel as though the way you style your site, the content you choose to put on it, and the way you interact with the people who stumble upon it are a far more accurate indicator of who you are as a person than a single page will ever be. By attempting to depict your entire online identity in the least offensive way possible on a single page, you effectively limit who you can be viewed as. You&#39;re defined by how you act, not how you tell people to think of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet users as a whole have grown far too used to taking the easiest, least offensive methods to define how they wish to be seen. People will use tone indicators as a way to hide what they really think under the thin veil of &amp;quot;/hj&amp;quot;, refusing to present their opinions in a genuine matter. In my eyes, the modern about me section is just an extension of this, people wanting to be universally liked, and fearing individualism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be disliked by some is to be an individual. There&#39;s no such thing as someone without opinions, and there will always be people who oppose the opinions you hold. The discourse that comes from this, whilst unpleasant, is extremely important in helping both parties mature as people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&#39;t hide behind about me sections, or anything else, just present yourself as you are. Some people may like you, some may not, but that&#39;s simply how life is. Your online identity is an extension of your person, and at times, it&#39;s important to treat it as such. Don&#39;t limit who you are just because you fear that someone else may disagree. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Computer Addiction in the Modern Era</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/computeraddiction/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/computeraddiction/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I&#39;d like to paint a picture for you all, it&#39;s a weekend, you have no work or school to worry about, what do you do? Do you go out and partake in your hobby perhaps, or maybe hang out with friends? No, you obviously sit at your desk and use your computer until you get tired again. This is just theoretical, of course, but if it sounds anything like you, odds are you&#39;re a computer addict. Welcome to the club, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Computer addiction in and of itself is something that would&#39;ve seemed incomprehensible just 25 years ago. However, over time computers have gained the ability to do significantly more than they were onced intended to do. This is a process I could probably spend an hour talking bout, but I&#39;ll sum it up in a few sentences. Computers used to be expensive, and as such, consumers didn&#39;t buy them, so consumer based programs didn&#39;t exist. Prices went down as more computers were made, and as such, the number of programs made for consumers increased. A bunch of wacky stuff happens, then bam, the internet, and bam, you have no social interaction outside of your AO3 proofreading Discord Server solely comprised of people living in different timezones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason so many people can be seen using their computers for absurd amounts of time is because of how much you can do on a computer now. Want to watch a movie or a show? Bet. Want to play some games? I gotchu man. Want to talk with some friends? Bet. Want to get an obscure question about the air vent trim on your E36 325i? Some old guy who&#39;s been a BMW technician for 50 years has got you covered. You don&#39;t need to go to a library to learn things anymore, you don&#39;t need to go out with frinds to hang out anymore. Everything is convenient now, arguably, too convenient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rarely does a day go by where I&#39;m not using my computer for at least a few hours, because I can gain so much knowledge and dopamine from it, so easily. It&#39;s just not rewarding to live life as people once did, sitting at your computer all day is objectively a more efficient way to do things. This thought process, however, is pretty terrible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more one grows used to the ease of life a computer brings them, the less one is able to deal with the hardships of everyday life. Why bother having real conversations when you can just DM someone and add &amp;quot;/j&amp;quot; to every message to prevent any consequences to your words? Computers are just another form of escapism, same as any other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Escapism, however, isn&#39;t always a bad thing, if one were to solely engage in the hardships of daily life, they&#39;d grow insane, the ease of use of the internet provides the perfect compliment to the hardships of daily life. However, when computer usage becomes your everyday life, your life itself begins to lose value. It&#39;s very difficult to feel satisfaction when nothing you do had work behind it. I simply feel as though I, along with many others, have grown far too dependent on how easy a life distanced from reality by an LCD screen is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t to say computers aren&#39;t a brilliant thing, by providing easy access to the internet, we have nearly infinite knowledge at out finger tips, computers are arguably the most useful tool humanity has created in centuries. Yet, computers are merely just that, a tool, something to provide assistance in your everyday life, but not to supplant it. Use computers as an aid for acquiring knowledge and social interaction, but not as your sole method for either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As with many things in life, computer usage is excellent in moderation, but terrible in excess. When used in excess you end up writing articles on computer addiction for your personal site, which is a terrible fate. That&#39;s all for today, take this one with a grain of salt, it&#39;s all based on my opinions, TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>My Pointless Web Design Pet Peeves</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/webdesignpetpeeves/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/webdesignpetpeeves/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Throughout life, I&#39;ve always been irregularly good at one thing, hating. I usually tend to keep this out of my blog, but these takes were obviously far too important to not share with my loyal 0.5 readers. I&#39;ve been working on recreational websites for a little over a month and a half now, and whilst I have learned what I like in designing websites, I also learned a lot about what bothers me in web design, in other words, pet peeves. The former is boring, and as aforementioned, I&#39;m a professional hater, so this&#39;ll be about the latter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I certainly could&#39;ve introduced the talking points of this article in the first paragraph, but that would almost make this too structured, and structure almost implies that I have valid criticisms, which I don&#39;t. So I&#39;ll start off here, I have always been irrationally bothered by absurdly large headers, I actually tried using one on this (questionable) webdev attempt:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/tm16.png&quot; alt=&quot; The unpublished version 1.6 of trademarkhell.net &quot; height=&quot;600px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a firm believer in substance over style, and this carries over to my current web design philosophy. By having a header which takes up a great deal of screen real estate, you&#39;re effectively reducing the functionality your site has prior to scrolling. This is exactly why I believe headers should be small relative to the main content area, for you can use the content to express yourself and add value to your site, as opposed to adding a silly image. Once more, these are all just my unfounded opinions, don&#39;t take them too seriously, unless you  agree with them, in which case they&#39;re completely evidence backed and real.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuing on the trend of web design pet peeves I&#39;ve picked up through personal failure, I&#39;ll be going over one of the greatest accessibility warcrimes, sites that expand horizontally as opposed to vertically. Just about any monitor of any size can handle a 900px wide site that goes down, but very few monitors can handle a 600px tall site that expands horizontally. Just because it works on your 1440p monitor doesn&#39;t mean everyone else should have to use a horizontal scrollbar. I speak from experience:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/tm152.png&quot; alt=&quot;Version 1.5 of trademarkhell.net &quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you can see, this is a site largely based on a horizontal layout, which whilst semi-cool looking, resulted in the majority of mobile or laptop users having a less than pleasant experience. This largely loops back to my previous point of substance over style, by making your site vertically built, it may lose some style points, but it gains a great deal of substance in the form of accessibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, these previous two points almost had too much backing evidence, so  I feel it&#39;s my duty to highlight one of my completely irrational pet peeves, sites with a bunch of gifs and images. I literally have no reason for disliking them, they look cool, but for some reason part of me takes this way too seriously and thinks people should cover their sites in their schizo ramblings instead of photos or whatever. Don&#39;t take this as advice from me, it sucks the soul out of your website, I mean, just look at mine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take this article as inspiration if you want, but I&#39;d highly advise not doing so. Web design is meant to be fun, do whatever the hell you want, I just wanted to write this for fun, as my form of web design fun is publishing my stupid ramblings. Have a good one, keep making cool sites, TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Local Car Culture as Viewed by an Idiot</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/carculture/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/carculture/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I think it&#39;s a mandate of every small town to have two things, a car scene solely comprised of riced out economy cars, and an excessive amount of unoccupied retail space. I can&#39;t really think of much to say about grocery stores that closed, so this article will be about the former.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel the need to preface this article by saying that I fell into these groups in my younger years (RIP &#39;92 Miata, you were a real one till the end), and this isn&#39;t intended to be a criticism of them. If I weren&#39;t moving countries in the near future, I&#39;d likely still own a shitbox of some variety (ignoring the fact i still have one). However, it is my duty as someone with an unreasonable interest in poorly modified vehicles to write about them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, generally speaking, the types of modified vehicles you&#39;ll see being driven around in my unnamed hellscape esque small town in the middle of the night can be divided into three categories. The Civic category, the not a Civic category, and the trust fund category. All three of these categories are occupied by teenage drivers of equal inexperience, but are not equal in terms of raw power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To start with, let me highlight &#39;ol reliable,&#39; the Honda Civic, it doesn&#39;t really matter what year, it could be 10 years old, it could be 25 years old, the modifications always remain the same. It&#39;s mandatory that the engine itself remains untouched, it wouldn&#39;t be a true broke secondary schooler vehicle otherwise. Rather, they invest all of their money into absurd 18&amp;quot; shining gold wheels that are usually spaced in a way completely disproportionate to the car body. One mustn&#39;t forget the most important component either, an absurdly large wing purchased from eBay, likely held on by adhesive strips. If you&#39;re looking to find these drivers, they can generally be found in ditches, and doing 70km on a 25km residential street.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, the second category, in practice, the modifications mentioned in the Civic category remain identical, but rather, the car changes. These are vehicles owned by true contrarians who want to defy societal norms, so instead of buying a Civic, they bought a Miata or a Corolla. These are cars that are objectively worse for a secondary school student, be it in convenience or reliability, but they represent a act of true defiance. Instead of taking to the streets and protesting, they did something braver, driving a mildly diferent vehicle. Deeply inspiring stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Society is inevitably divided into social classes, this is a fundamental principle of humanity following the agricultural revolution, yet, some people remain in a fringe category between the two. These are those that fall into the trust fund category, those with enough wealth to get an absurd vehicle, yet simultaneously lack the intellect or wealth to attend an educational institution outside of the unremarkable town in which you reside. The trust fund, unsurprisingly maintains the same modifications as the previous categories, but not due to a lack of funds.Rather, they maintain these modifications because they have no idea what they&#39;re looking at in the engine bay, and are currently contacting their vehicle&#39;s manufacturer to ask about blinker fluid. These pseudo-nepotists can be found driving brand new WRXs, EVOs, and in some cases, Civic SIs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of these categories actually know how to drive, and their semi-annual attempts at street racing result in three cars ending up in a ditch, and them waiting another six months to try and street race again. Those who belong to these categories either mature into automotive enthusiasts who look fondly upon their days as an idiotic student, or simply move on with life and get an unremarkable vehicle as most do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article is of absolutely no substance and I solely wrote it for fun, it&#39;s more or less just a way for me to mess with falvor text whilst recounting things I see around time. Thanks for reading this if you did, for some reason, I apopreciate it. TM out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Personal Information and the Indie Web</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/infoprivacy/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/infoprivacy/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I think just about everyone has heard the generic preamble about internet privacy before, &amp;quot;blah blah don&#39;t say your name and location blah blah,&amp;quot; but, I&#39;ve begun to notice that some people didn&#39;t take this one to heart when it comes to personal sites. So, before I say anything else, please, for the love of god, don&#39;t put your location and full legal name on your site, or your age, especially if you&#39;re a minor. I keep seeing sites that start with &amp;quot;hey guys i&#39;m 13, my name is [FULL LEGAL NAME], i live in [STATE/PROVINCE/PREFECTURE] and this is my site&amp;quot; and then proceed to link their Discord. Please don&#39;t do this, people on the internet are weird.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/mynameiswalter.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot; Walter White from Breaking Bad during his confession &quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
(I felt my article would be incomplete if I didn&#39;t include a screenshot of this)
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t to say you can&#39;t have an about webmaster page (although i also kinda dislike those, but that&#39;s another day&#39;s article), or write about stuff you like in a blog, but maybe just talk about what you&#39;re interested in, rather than the exact person you are. Personal sites, in my opinion, are meant to serve as places to depict who you are based on your interests and actions, rather than based on literal personal information. I think it&#39;s extremely important to keep this in mind whenever you do just about anything on your site. As the old saying goes, albeit, I don&#39;t think it was meant to be used in this context, &amp;quot;Let your actions speak for themselves.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m not just saying all this because I&#39;m some fiend for anonymity (I mean I am), but rather, because I think some people are genuinely putting themselves at risk by putting so much info in an easy to access place. The world&#39;s a lot smaller than you think it is, especially if you live in a heavily populated country with a lot of internet usage. Keep that in mind. Anyways, TM out, don&#39;t dox yourself, bye.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>I Owe a Lot to Welcome to the N.H.K.</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/nhk/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/nhk/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This article spoils A LOT about Welcome to the N.H.K. and isn&#39;t really a review of it, it&#39;s a bit different than my other articles about anime, but I really wanted to write it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the N.H.K. is, for all intents and purposes, an unremarkable anime, light novel, and manga series from the 2000s. Featuring animation that didn&#39;t age particularly well, time-period correct degeneracy, and a cast of characters, that appear to be rather generic at first glance. I, however, being the brave explorer that I was in 2021, chose to watch it, and to be honest, it was probably one of the best choices I&#39;ve made in my life, which seems weird to say about an anime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/nhk.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot; The coverart of the aforementioned Welcome to the N.H.K.&quot; height=&quot;500px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;N.H.K. originally released as a light novel in 2002, written by Tatsuhiko Takimoto, and illustrated by Yoshitonshi Abe, it was later adapted into a manga in 2003, which was illustrated by Kenji Oiwa, and into an anime by Studio Gonzo in 2008. I&#39;ve only seen the anime, and have no intention of experiencing the former two, so it&#39;ll be the focus of this article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;N.H.K. follows Tatsuhiro Satou, everyone&#39;s favorite Terry A. Davis esque delusional and suicidal NEET shut-in. The show has several interesting characters, but for the sake of leaving some of the more absurd elements of the show for you, I won&#39;t go over them, rather, I&#39;ll just highlight the heroine, Misaki Nakahara. Misaki is an equally delusional individual who seeks to somehow save Satou from his NEEThood, yet in the process they just end up making eachother worse. That&#39;s it, that&#39;s basically the plot of the show.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m sure it seems as though this show is just another piece of fodder to watch or ignore based on what I&#39;ve said alone, but quite frankly, what happens in the show isn&#39;t what makes it so impactful, the bulk of the events in the show solely serve as comedic relief.(blah blah blah mild spoiler warning)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rather, what makes the show impactful is how it ends, or more so, how it doesn&#39;t. Satou just has to go out and get a minimum wage job, he&#39;s still delusional, he still wants to be a NEET, but he has no money. Satou just goes out and becomes a productive member of society, not out of choice, but by necesity. Something about how non-comedic this was as opposed to the rest of the show really stuck with me, especially as someone in a similar position at time, functionally being a NEET due to my university being closed, and seriously considering just dropping everything and doing nothing with the rest of my life but sitting around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being a NEET shut-in always seems appealing to a lot of people, and I think N.H.K. really shows that well, so much of the show is just comedic relief, as if showing why you SHOULD just lock yourself in your room and never leave. Yet, it ends with this slap to your face, that nothing will ever happen if you don&#39;t go out and accept life. Satou doesn&#39;t seem to be happy about joining the workforce, but he was equally delusional and suicidal as a shut-in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re going to be unhappy, you may as well be productive while you do it, and at least give yourself a chance to become happy. That&#39;s what I took from the show, and quite frankly, I owe my social life and academics to this show, as I probably would&#39;ve just kept rotting away as I did during COVID if not for the reality check this show gave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn&#39;t that good of a show, and I&#39;ve barely actually mentioned anything about it, but trust me, there&#39;s a lot of impactful elements in it, and a decent bit of funny segments, honestly, if anything I said stuck with you, just watch the show. It&#39;ll probably hit a different chord than most of the seemingly &amp;quot;life changing&amp;quot; shows were meant to. This isn&#39;t Evangelion, this isn&#39;t Cowboy Bepop, it&#39;s not some deep freudian psychological thing, it&#39;s just a reality check. Tm out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>SSGs Are Good, Actually</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ssg/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ssg/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This article is sorta an addendum to my previous article about people not using blogs, so read that first if you want to. Anyways, people don&#39;t seem to like SSGs, as my friend bravely demonstrated here in an act of true determination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/ssgslander.png&quot; alt=&quot; SSG SLANDER!!!&quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;His brave sacrifice will be immortalized through this article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dislike of SSGs, from my observations seems to stem from two primary sources, people feeling as though it looks too difficult, and people who feel it takes the &amp;quot;fun&amp;quot; out of website creation. For the sake of maintaining rationality, I&#39;ll primarily be focusing on the former, until I get bored, in which case I will certainly rant about the latter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I fully understand why many people feel as though SSGs look difficult, I mean you&#39;re going from a few HTML and CSS files to whatever the hell this is...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/sitecomposition.png&quot; alt=&quot; The file structure of the site you&#39;re reading this on&quot; height=&quot;800px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;However, the barrier to entry of reading a few docs (or a 6 minute video... https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kzf9A9tkkl4) is very much worth the ease of use you gain, and nowadays, a lot of static site generators seem to be easy to set up in mere minutes. (I hear good things about Hugo, I of course chose the one SSG with terrible documentation and like two tutorials, shoutout to 11ty). The benefit of using an SSG isn&#39;t in how easy they are to set up (in my opinion...), but rather, how easy they make maintaining your site. This whole article is being written on a single markdwon document, I haven&#39;t even touched HTML or CSS for it, my SSG does all the work for me, provided I give it the templates needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Building on yesterdays point, and the words of an anonymous commenter that I agree with, a large part of why there&#39;s so many untouched blogs on the Indie Web is because of how much work it takes to publish an article without an SSG. People need to manually create new HTML and CSS files, and format the whole thing with HTML text elements, which, speaking from experience, is a pain in the ass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I encourage literally anyone looking to update or remake their sites to at least try using an SSG when they do it, all you need to do is follow the documentation and give it a few templates, after that, maintaining your site is as simple as writing. Don&#39;t be one of those people that has whole sections of their sites that they update once every two years, use an SSG. It&#39;s that easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, before I finish this article up, I feel it&#39;s my duty to address the not using an SSG being &amp;quot;fun&amp;quot; part of the argument, and I&#39;ll do so in a single sentence. If it&#39;s so fun to run your website without an SSG, why do you never post anything???? (and if you do maitnain a blog without an SSG, shoutout to you, but there&#39;s something wrong with you)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: SSGs make everything easier and save your firstborn child&#39;s life, use them or suffer. Tm out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Please Actually Use Your Blog Sections</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/useyourblog/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/useyourblog/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tm here, if you haven&#39;t noticed, I quite like writing blog articles, in fact, I&#39;ve been publishing them daily since I made this site revision (albeit, i don&#39;t expect this pace to continue forever). As such, I feel it is my duty to preach the gospel of article creation, for I&#39;ve encountered many sites which have entire sections dedicated to this practice, yet rarely, if ever, publish blog articles. I&#39;m here to put a stop to this heresy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contrary to popular belief, running a blog actually serves a purpose outside of filing the section of your site that you had no idea what to do with. In my opinion, blogs are the best way to capture your mental state at a given time. A case could be made for diaries, of course, but diaries merely serve to recount events, not what you truly think from an external perspective. Blogs capture the way you think and act, even if it&#39;s just through your writing mannerisms. Furthermore, I feel as though the self restraint induced from publishing blogs publically leads to a more accurate depiction of how one truly behaved at the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In effect, what I&#39;m trying to depict, is that, blogs can actually be useful tools to look back on who you are/were as a person, whilst also honing your writing skills for no real reason. Blogs can be a lot more than obligatory sections on your website that you ignore, and I really hope people realize that. You don&#39;t have to make a blog, but honestly, don&#39;t bother putting the section on your site if you don&#39;t intend to use it. Oh, also, maybe refrain from putting your extremist 4chan political takes on your blogs, just a word of advice. Tm out, this one&#39;s a short post, but I have nothing more to say on the matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/osakaism.png&quot; alt=&quot;osaka with the autism hat?????&#39;&quot; height=&quot;600px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;pic unrelated&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The 2000s Happened; Haruhi Suzumiya</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/haruhi/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/haruhi/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;blah blah blah; obligatory disclaimer goes here: show discussed was rated 13+ in most countries, putting this here so i don&#39;t get sued., thank you COPPA ..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When people think of the 2000s, they probably think about things like the 2008 recession or the dawn of the new millenium, but I have my priorities in check; I think about anime. More specifically, I think of Kyoto Animation&#39;s adaptions of manga, light novels, and visual novels, like Clannad, Kanon, Lucky Star, and The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya. The former three are arguably still relevant today, even if just watched for nostalgia, but curiously, it seems as though Haruhi has largely faded into relative obscurity. I personally think it&#39;s a shame that so few people know about Haruhi nowadays, so I&#39;m taking responsibility and preaching the gospel of this show that I really like, despite it having no exceptional characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumyia aired it&#39;s first season in Spring of 2006, to largely positive reviews. It adapted the light novel series of thes same name, which had it&#39;s first novel released in 2003, and is not yet complete. The anime series, however, seems to be significantly better known, and in my opinion, is the superior way to consume the arcs it adapts, and as such, is the focus of this article. Attached below is the art of the movie because I think it goes too hard not to include, and it shows the cast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/haruhiposter.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The poster of the movie &#39;The Disappearence of Haruhi Suzumiya&#39;&quot; height=&quot;600px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The show is told from the point of view of Kyon, a character with no actual name, nor a last name. He served as one of the original &amp;quot;straight man&amp;quot; characters in anime, a trend which seems to have become rather common today. Complimenting him is a cast of proportionately, but for the sake of not sucking the joy out of whoever chooses to watch this show, I&#39;ll just highlight the namesake of the show, Haruhi Suzumiya. Haruhi is a delusional character with god-like powers who effectively has the ability to do whatever she wants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the final sentence of the last paragraph didn&#39;t make it obvious enough, this is, in effect, a show about Haruhi doing whatever she wills, with whoever she wills. In effect, this makes the show a slice of life, and it evidently is, but what makes the show interesting is the fact that Haruhi can do just about anything, and as such, many of the activities diverge from that of the standard &amp;quot;cute girls doing cute things&amp;quot; formula. The show can get pretty batshit insane, in a very good way. I&#39;ll attach the clip below as a testament to that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/x3GgMehORTI?si=mO3lUjgxr9W21T58&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could probably provide context to this clip, but instead I&#39;m just going to end my article here. Watch the show. It&#39;s aged terribly, but man, when it hits, it hits. Batshit insane slice of life with an interesting cast. It won&#39;t be the best show you&#39;ve ever watched or anything, but it&#39;s enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Top ten worst  interests; Polish Rock</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/polishrock/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/polishrock/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As a terminally online individual, who&#39;s life revolves around a select group of internet forums and Discord servers, it&#39;s my duty to exclusively maintain interests  that are either solely maintained by terminally online people, or maintained by 2.5 people total. As this website probably indicates, I&#39;ve fulfilled this requirement quite well, and today I&#39;ll be talking about one of the stranger ones. Polish Rock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few years ago I played through the game &#39;SUPERHOT&#39;, the most innovative shooter I&#39;ve played in years, but this isn&#39;t about SUPERHOT, rather, it&#39;s about the song that played in it&#39;s credits, &amp;quot;Psy Pawowa&amp;quot;, by Republika.&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;60&quot; src=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/14l0W9762h2UZpwtEq2mcV5EPUa48b8Yz/preview?usp=drivesdk&quot;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In hindsight, this is honestly one of the weaker songs on Republika&#39;s discography, but I think it&#39;s important for the rabbithole it led me down. It effectively made me realize that music I couldn&#39;t understand was actually pretty good, and opened the floodgates of Polish rock to me, as opposed to the same few Chinese and Japanese songs I was listening to at the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ironically, I still have no real interest in learning Polish, but, I have continued to discover many more bands and songs hailing from Poland. Just to list off a few, Turbo has a pretty strong discography, with nearly all the songs from their &#39;00 album &amp;quot;Remix 92&amp;quot; sounding really good, and Kazik na ywo has a really good collection of grunge-esque songs, albeit, the mastering on some of them leaves something to be desired (also pretty similar to grunge songs of the era...)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Republika has still remained my favorite of the Polish bands I&#39;ve heard, perhaps because they were the first, or perhaps due to the sheer number of songs they have. My favorites are easily &amp;quot;Fast (New)&amp;quot;, and &amp;quot;Raz na milion lat&amp;quot;. The latter of which is one of my favorite songs of all time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, despite this article largely being about my dumb interests and such, I would like for the 0.5 people reading this to at least consider listening to music from regions and languages outside of where they reside. It can be a really interesting experience, and if you&#39;re lucky (or unlucky), you may actually like the music. Anyways, that&#39;s it for today&#39;s rambling session, thanks for coming. Leave your bingoboards where you picked them up.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>The Indie Web Described By a True Idiot</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/indieweb/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/indieweb/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As of late( well not really, more so for the past 15 years ), the concept of the &#39;Indie Web&#39; has been in resurgence, with many seeking to partake in an internet free of the constraints of corporations or ruling powers, as the internet once was. Despite this, I&#39;d argue that the term &#39;Indie Web&#39; has really lost it&#39;s original meaning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This term suggests that these websites are truly independent from external influence, yet, the majority of self-declared &#39;Indie&#39; sites are still being hosted on services such as Neocities or Nekoweb, both of which have their own external rules and the ability to delete/moderate sites. These rules, of course, exist for reasons, but it&#39;s because of this external influence that I feel it&#39;s disingenous to say that these websites are truly &#39;Indie&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the modern sense being an independent site seems to be more of a design philosophy than that of a literal thing. The &#39;Indie Web&#39; seems to be defined by sites, which, for lack of better terminology, serve no real purpose. Take this site for example, it just serves to host my pretentious ramblings. The purposes of these sites suit their owners and, at times, a select group of people, but rarely venture outside of that small niche.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I&#39;m trying to say is that, in effect, &#39;Indie Web&#39; no longer means websites independent from external influence, rather, it means sites made for self indulgence, sites made for recreation rather than for profit, sites made by hobbyists, for hobbyists. Despite losing it&#39;s original meaning, I&#39;d argue that the concept of the &#39;Indie Web&#39; is stronger than ever, with more websites made for leisure existing now than there has been in years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, I&#39;d like to specify that this article is not a criticism of the &#39;Indie Web&#39; whatsoever, given I&#39;m an avid participant in the community. This article merely serves to provide an exteremly unscientific, and unproven theory as to what the &#39;Indie Web&#39; truly is, in it&#39;s current evolution. Albeit, I suspect that the defenition of the &#39;Indie Web&#39; will continue to change for as long as people continue to make websites for non commercial use.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>My Irrational Love for Monogatari</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/monogatariseries/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/monogatariseries/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;blah blah blah; obligatory disclaimer goes here: show discussed was rated 18+ in most countries, putting this here so i don&#39;t get sued., thank you COPPA ..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Monogatari Series, published originally in light novel form by Nisio Isin in 2005, adapted into a manga by Oh! Great in 2013, and adapted into an anime by Studio Shaft in 2009 is probably one of the most, if not the most problematic series to come out of Japan. I&#39;ve consumed the series in all of these formats numerous times, but for the sake of accessibility to the bulk of people, I&#39;ll be predominantly highlighting the first season of the anime, for the sake of convenience, and for the sake of spoilers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that nightmare of a starting sentence, you&#39;re probably wondering what exactly is so bad about this series, and why I&#39;m shilling it to you. I don&#39;t really intend to tone down what&#39;s wrong about this series, in fact, I&#39;ll summarize it in a single sentence. I genuinely think it&#39;s impossible to find a series that juxtaposes masterful wriiting with pure degeneracy like the Monogatari series. There&#39;s plenty of other problematic shows, but people solely watch them because they&#39;re problematic, so they don&#39;t exactly fall into the same category as Monogatari.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could probably go on and on about what&#39;s wrong with this series, but quite frankly, there&#39;s plenty of people who&#39;ve done it better than me, including the first 30 seconds of the show, find the show on your streaming service of choice, or elsewhere, and watch the first 30 seconds of Bakemonogatari, I was going to attach it here, but then I realized that my website host probably wouldn&#39;t appreciate that, so come back after you do that, or don&#39;t, I&#39;m not your dad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, before I expalin what I like about the series (and there&#39;s a lot), I feel I should probably give some context as to who I was when I first consumed it, you see, I was the prime demographic for being able to ignore all of the borderline insanity I mentioned above, I was in my early teens. Quite frankly, I probably wouldn&#39;t touch the show with a 50 meter pole if I didn&#39;t get into the series then, as I don&#39;t think I&#39;d be able to turn a blind eye to a lot of the things in the show if I watched it for the first time now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, okay, the four paragraphs of disclaimers are done, I can get into what I wanted to write this for, now. I think the Monogatari Series has some of the most compelling characters, and easily, the best animation style of any modern anime. This show relies heavily on 25 minute long episodes that are solely comprised of a few monologues, or a single conversation, yet it&#39;s because of how fleshed out these characters are that they don&#39;t feel boring, it genuinely feels as though you&#39;re watching a standard conversation. Studio Shaft, however, not wanting for the viewer to get bored, relies on a visual style unlike any other series (except for other Shaft series) to provide visual stimulation to the watcher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I obviously can&#39;t simply attach a full episode here to demonstrate the style, so instead, here&#39;s a trailer to the prequel of the series, which still shares that distinctive visual style:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1LEEczLPFlvbKm8x4PSBoJ6aYjA-hsR0y/preview?usp=drivesdk&quot;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I honestly would love to ramble on about this franchise for ages, but quite frankly, if what I said didn&#39;t make you hate the show, then you should watch it, if it did, then don&#39;t. That&#39;s basically it. I did what I could to shill it, and also did what I could to scare you away from it. My job here is done, I think..&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Failure and Webdesign</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ihatewebdesign/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/ihatewebdesign/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;About three weeks ago now, in the middle of July, I came to a sudden revelation, one, which, for a lesser man, may have caused great mental distress. I realized that my website completely sucked, was borderline impossible to modify, and was almost illegible. I, however, being the brave warrior that I am, chose not to let this decrease my morale, and instead set off on a brave journey to improve my site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For context, allow me to present the website that I had at the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/tm152.png&quot; alt=&quot;Version 1.5 of trademarkhell.net &quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s not bad... per se, especially given it was the product of me learning html the day before, but it&#39;s not good. It&#39;s very obviously the product of someone with little to no knowledge of compatability and the fundamentals of webdesign. I built content out horizontally instead overtically because I thought it looked cool, but that also meant that anyone with a monitor smaller than 1080p had to scroll to the side. I also had the brilliant idea of making the site yellow, orange, and white, which whilst pretty good for creamsicles, is god-awful for websites. Reading this site is a similar experience to trying to read grey text on a black background whilst wearing sunglasses. It was also built with no knowledge of flexbox, solely relying on CSS Grids, and no static site generator, so it was basically impossible for me to add more content to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a lot of ways, it was a fitting site for what it was, a site in it&#39;s infacy, and similar to infants, it was pretty useless. In an exercise of great stupidity, I thought that the best way to fix this was to suck any personality the site had out of it. I created a soulless husk of a website that was solely black and white, which had a layout that served no purpose outside of being utilitarian. Shockingly, a personal website that&#39;s meant to express your creativity that was made with no creativity isn&#39;t that appealing, here&#39;s a photo of it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/tm16.png&quot; alt=&quot; The unpublished version 1.6 of trademarkhell.net &quot; height=&quot;500px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, I quickly realized that Melankorin may be the only one actually able to make a visually appealing monochrome site, and quickly moved onto my next valiant attempt at webdesign, not yet feeling dejected (which I soon would be). For this layout, I thought, logically, if colorful backgrounds for text were too much, and if black and white was too boring, why not make the best of both worlds. This then led me to what may be the ultimate example of style over substance. It&#39;s cool, I won&#39;t deny that, but nothing really &amp;quot;clicked&amp;quot; for me with this site, it just, wasn&#39;t what I wanted. I admittedly don&#39;t have much to say about it, but here it is, even more unfinished than the last layout:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/tm17.png&quot; alt=&quot; The unpublished version 1.7 of trademarkhell.net &quot; height=&quot;500px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re now stepping into the territory of layouts I have literally no memory of making, so this should be interesting. At this point I was so engrossed in making the perfect website, that I wasn&#39;t even drafting layouts on paper anymore, I was just making them and crossing my fingers, and this also meant that I was making even less progress before dropping them immediately. There was about four layouts I did this for, and quite frankly they&#39;re all so unfinished that I don&#39;t feel the need to attach more than one image, but, here it is, the pinnacle of modern webdesign (i honestly don&#39;t know what this was meant to be???):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/tmv17.png&quot; alt=&quot; The unpublished version 1.8 of trademarkhell.net &quot; height=&quot;500px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point, I had more drafts of webdesigns on paper than I could count, thinking that if my previous attempts didn&#39;t work, I&#39;d surely get a sudden revelation at some point, but, I never did, and so, I randomly picked a layout, and now that layout is the site you&#39;re on. I don&#39;t really &amp;quot;like&amp;quot; this layout, but, it meets the bare minimum of what I wanted. It has color, but not too much. It has visual elements, but not too many. It has various templates for webpages, but not too many. I&#39;ll redo this website eventually, but the issue is, I can&#39;t find anything wrong with this layout, I don&#39;t like it, but I don&#39;t know why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This layout, in my eyes, is a failure, but to be fair, so were all the previous ones, I suspect webdesign for me will always be me chasing the high I think i&#39;ll get if I make a website I like,  I don&#39;t know if that will ever happen, but I&#39;m glad it probably won&#39;t, as it gives me a reason to keep working on websites, which others seem to like. Anyways, thanks for reading this ramble, my other posts should be more interesting, but I&#39;ve wanted to write this one since my first failed layout.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>(my obsession with) Crappy Old Tech</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/lowqualityoldtech/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/lowqualityoldtech/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I accidentally procured the extremely unfortunate hobby of collecting and restoring old technology, I&#39;ll probably write more extensively about this in another article, but that&#39;s not related to the point. Despite this hobby, some of my favorite pieces of technology are the arguably worthless pieces of low-quality black plastic that came out from the late 80s to the late 90s, that I&#39;ve done aproximately zero work on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These things have absolutely zero reason to still work, they were made using extremely primitive computerized systems, that honestly had no place being in them, yet, for some reason, they seem impossible to kill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take this TV, it&#39;s a 13&amp;quot; RCA CRT that probably costed about 50 bucks new. It has no connections on it other than RF, and has remarkebly below average (but not bad!) video quality. It&#39;s been sitting to my right on my desk, playing random anime, everyday, for at least five hours, for five years now, and god knows what it went through before I got it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/tmcrt.jpg&quot; alt=&quot; My 13 inch RCA CRT &quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is insignificant enough that I didn&#39;t even bother moving it from it&#39;s eternal resting place to take a photo of it, I feel it&#39;s extremely important that I capture this device with it&#39;s natural lighting, and natural positioning. I legitimately have no idea why this thing still works, but I&#39;ll be sad when it stops working. The black magic that keeps this thing alive, along with many other devices that had the misfortune of being created in the &amp;quot;shitty black plastic&amp;quot; era of technological design is exactly why I love them so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I do feel it&#39;s my duty to reflect that, despite the title of this article, some of these &amp;quot;crappy&amp;quot; pieces of old tech are held in high regard. Take this attached photo (ignore the cassette deck on top, that is actual crap but i love it dearly)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/tmhifi.png&quot; alt=&quot; My desks HiFi Stack &quot; height=&quot;400px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Picutred above (but below the cassette deck, once again, it still sucks, once again, I still use it daily and love it) is the Luxman R-115, something, which to the layman, is a prime example of black plastic crap. Despite it&#39;s appearence, however, it&#39;s generally regarded as one of the best amplifiers of the late 80s. I&#39;m listening to it as I write this article, and it&#39;s powered the speakers I use with my computer for years now, and I strongly agree with this statement. It doesn&#39;t look nearly as good as the silver faced equipment I use in my main HiFi stack, but man, it sounds good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the inherently satirical nature of the title of this article, I feel it&#39;s my duty to &amp;quot;enlighten&amp;quot; the masses that despite the awful appearence of technology from this era, it really holds up, and sometimes, it&#39;s even good. I have a lot more tech from this era that I use often, but this article would be pointlessly long if I covered them. Basically, TLDR, ugly old tech cool, ugly old tech good.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Yeah, Breakcore Sucks (but i love it)</title>
		<link href="https://trademarkhell.net/blog/breakcore/"/>
		<updated>2024-08-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://trademarkhell.net/blog/breakcore/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Breakcore, the official genre of 20-something NEETs that describe themselves as &amp;quot;lainpilled femcels&amp;quot; and use PFPs of Tomoko from WataMote in their extremist political Discords. This genre (according to the reputable source of Wikipedia) traces it&#39;s routes to the mid 90s, stemming from jungle, drum and bass, and other relatively small gneres, however, this form of Breakcore is so detached from what many consider to be modern Breakcore that I&#39;ll be skipping to the 2000s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, picture this, it&#39;s the late 2000s, you have to pick between three CDs, first, we have the objectively good CD, &amp;quot;Graduation&amp;quot; by Kanye West, with it&#39;s bright album art, but obviously, you won&#39;t pick this one, because you&#39;re here on this article. Beside it, you have &amp;quot;Detrimentalist&amp;quot; by Venetian Snares, which dawns fittingly complex album art, and &amp;quot;tomboyish love for daughter&amp;quot; by Goreshit, which featurees album art that is likely illegal in several regions. The latter two, in my opinion, represent the two quintessential Breakcore albums of the 2000s that led to the two branching Breakcore sub-genres that we see today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://trademarkhell.net/img/2x1.png&quot; alt=&quot; The album art of Detrimentalist by Venetian Snares and toboyish love for daughter by Goreshit &quot; height=&quot;300px&quot; style=&quot;display: block; margin: 0 auto&quot;&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Now, I know what you&#39;re thinking &amp;quot;what tf makes thse albums important&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;wtf is that goreshit album art.&amp;quot; I&#39;ll get to the first point briefly, but the album art is, you guessed it, cropped Touhou hentai. This is truly a genre defined by it&#39;s classiness and maturity. Now, back to the first point, these albums, whilst quite good, are arguably most important due to the cultural split they caused in breakcore. Take this song from Goreshit&#39;s album, titled &amp;quot;strawberry cheesecake&amp;quot;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;60&quot; src=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Ps5KFM_7DbCy-CoMHW99eNLHELdnY7Jx/preview?usp=drivesdk&quot;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then compare it to this song, &amp;quot;Gentlemen&amp;quot; by Venetian Snares:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe frameborder=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;400&quot; height=&quot;60&quot; src=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1MuksT2iE1mdgb-bE6yJJA-VQm7L8UKQ0/preview?usp=drivesdk&quot;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These songs, despite both being Breakcore, due to their usage of the Amen Break, arguably couldn&#39;t be any more different. Goreshit leans heavily towards sampling sounds and music from Anime, a trend that continues today in Breakcore through artists such as Rori in early 20s, and to a limited degree, through Sewerslvt&#39;s works (although it can be argued that the majority of her music isn&#39;t breakcore, and I largely agree with this). The latter represents a more traditional form of Breakcore, which is the other side of the modern Breakcore coin, being evident through artists such as Machine Girl, and once again, to a lesser extent, Nanoray.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally enjoy both genres of Breakcore, being a terminally online individual, but the point of this article wasn&#39;t really to say that &amp;quot;yeah i kinda like breakcore lol&amp;quot;, but rather, to demonstrate the sheer variety of Breakcore artists and songs. Many people do disregard Breakcore, for good reason, but for those that haven&#39;t already, listen to some, you&#39;ll probably like at least some of it, unless you don&#39;t, in which case, it&#39;s not my problem.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
